mycrazygoodlife.com 2019-07-03

# Policies - My Crazy Good Life

## Policies for Crazy Good Media and My Crazy Good Life

Effective date: May 17, 2019

###  **Affiliate Links**

Affiliate links are used on this site. This means that when you click the link on my site (for example, an Amazon.com link) and make a purchase, I could earn a small percentage of commission for your purchase. This does not charge you any more than it would normally, it’s just a thank you from the site for referring traffic. I use affiliate links because it’s a way that I can afford to bring you great content for free. I participate in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

###  **Comment Policy**

Your policy will be approved and published as long as it doesn’t contain the following: spammy links, hateful or hurtful language, or irrelevant content. I reserve the right to delete any comment on my site.

### Disclosure Policy

 **I sometimes review products or services without being compensated.** I do this so that I can share my thoughts on these products with you.  **I will sometimes receive free products or services to review** , and will only write about those products if I can do so in an honest way. If I were to receive a product that I did not care for I would not recommend it to you. **Sometimes, I receive monetary compensation to write about a product, service, or business.** I may tell you about a product that I haven’t had personal experience with. If I receive free product or monetary compensation about a product, I will add a disclosure to the beginning and/or end of the post telling you so. Advertisers: all links on My Crazy Good Life are no-follow. No exceptions.

I close giveaways within 24 hours of them ending, unless an emergency comes up (I am a mom first, you know!). I’ll contact the winner via email and the winner will have 48 hours to contact me back unless otherwise noted in my email.

###  **Links to other websites**

My Crazy Good Life contains links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave this blog, you should note that I do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, I cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

###  **How My Crazy Good Life  uses cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

This blog uses traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps me analyze data about web page traffic and improve my website in order to tailor it to customer needs and wants. I only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help me provide you with a better website, by enabling me to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives this blog access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

###  **Advertising**

I use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on my website, which allows me to bring you the great content you see here. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Some of my advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. I do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. I may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website and these vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

##  **Privacy Policy for Crazy Good Media/My Crazy Good Life**

Crazy Good Media, LLC (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://mycrazygoodlife.com website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://mycrazygoodlife.com

###  **Definitions**

* Service

Service is the https://mycrazygoodlife.com website operated by Crazy Good Media, LLC

* Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

* Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

* Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).

* Data Controller

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.

* Data Processors (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

* Data Subject (or User)

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.

##  **Information Collection And Use**

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

##  **Types of Data Collected**

###  **Personal Data**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address  
* First name and last name  
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City  
* Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

###  **Usage Data**

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

###  **Affiliate Data**

Affiliate links are used on this site. This means that when you click the link on my site (for example, an Amazon.com link) and make a purchase, I could earn a small percentage of commission for your purchase. This does not charge you any more than it would normally, it’s just a thank you from the site for referring traffic. I use affiliate links because it’s a way that I can afford to bring you great content for free. I participate in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. I also participate in Share A Sale.

###  **Tracking & Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.  
* Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences  
and various settings.  
* Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

###  **Use of Data**

Crazy Good Media, LLC uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service  
* To notify you about changes to our Service  
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so  
* To provide customer support  
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service  
* To monitor the usage of our Service  
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues  
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

###  **Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection  ** **Regulation (GDPR)**  
—————————————————————————————-

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Crazy Good Media, LLC legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Crazy Good Media, LLC may process your Personal Data because:

* We need to perform a contract with you  
* You have given us permission to do so  
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by  
your rights  
* For payment processing purposes  
* To comply with the law

 **Retention of Data**

Crazy Good Media, LLC will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Crazy Good Media, LLC will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

 **Transfer Of Data**

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Crazy Good Media, LLC will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and  
no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

##  **Disclosure Of Data**

###  **Business Transaction**

If Crazy Good Media, LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

###  **Disclosure for Law Enforcement**

Under certain circumstances, Crazy Good Media, LLC may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

###  **Legal Requirements**

Crazy Good Media, LLC may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation  
* To protect and defend the rights or property of Crazy Good Media, LLC  
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the  
Service  
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public  
* To protect against legal liability

###  **Security Of Data**

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100%  
secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**  
—————————————————————————

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Crazy Good Media, LLC aims to take reasonable steps to  
allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.

* The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.

* The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.

* The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.

* The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.

* The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Crazy Good Media, LLC relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

###  **Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

###  **Analytics**

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

* Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add- on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy &amp; Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

###  **Payments**

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are: PayPal

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

###  **Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s  
site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

###  **Children’s Privacy**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

###  **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of  
this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this  
page.

###  **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email: becca@crazygoodmedia.com
